{
    "subject": "Nancy_Juvonen",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Jimmy_Fallon",
    "human_readable": "Nancy Juvonen is married to Jimmy Fallon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9647886753082275,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Nancy Juvonen and Jimmy Fallon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9208444356918335,
            "question": "To whom is Nancy Juvonen married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9160557389259338,
            "question": "Who is Nancy Juvonen married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8861464858055115,
            "question": "Who are Nancy Juvonen and Jimmy Fallon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8235484957695007,
            "question": "Is Jimmy Fallon married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7464179396629333,
            "question": "Who is Nancy Juvonen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6267207264900208,
            "question": "What is the name of Jimmy Fallon's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35536497831344604,
            "question": "What is the profession of Jimmy Fallon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.351106196641922,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Jimmy Fallon's personal life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20735229551792145,
            "question": "Name a celebrity couple."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nancy Juvonen is married to Jimmy Fallon.",
            "html": "yago_17309_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Jimmy Fallon's personal life?",
            "html": "yago_17309_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the profession of Jimmy Fallon?",
            "html": "yago_17309_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Jimmy Fallon's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_17309_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_17309_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\nThe context information confirms that Jimmy Fallon is married to Nancy Juvonen, as stated in various documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17309/re-ranker-msmarco/66.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_17309/re-ranker-msmarco/95.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently provide information that confirms Nancy Juvonen is married to Jimmy Fallon, including details such as their wedding date and the fact that they have children together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}